

PERSONAL

- Name Iraj Ahang
- **Address** 271 Kings Road, Chorlton Cum Hardy Manchester M21 0XG
- Phone number 07460077744
- Email rustamahang@gmail.com
- Date of birth 04-04-1993
- **Nationality** Male
- **Driving licence**
- LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/moha iraj-ahang-462a44138/

INTERESTS

- Team sports
- Reading
- Travelling
- Running
- Learning languages

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian Russian **English** Dari Farsi



IRAJ AHANG

I am a hardworking and ambitious individual with a great passion for IT Support. I have excellent communication skills, enabling me to effectively communicate with a wide range of people. I am seeing a full-time position in the industry in which I can put into practice my knowledge and experience, ultimately benefiting the operations of the organisation that I work for.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Sep 2015 - Dec 2016 Counselor Assistant

Embassy of Afghanistan, Kyiv

Jan 2017 - May 2019 Translator

UNHCR Right to Protection, Kyiv

Highly skilled and experienced Translator with a strong background in translating legal documents in English, Russian, Ukrainian, Farsi and Dari. Bringing forth an excellent command of these languages, and a track record of impeccable proofreading, editing and translating. Adept in accurately assessing the context of material, translating it in an understandable and appropriate way. Highly skilled in legal terminology and processes, helping clients to better understand their rights and position. Bringing forth a positive work ethic and a commitment to efficiency and integrity.

Jun 2019 - Jan 2020

Sales Manager

Tutopt, Kyiv

- Coaches team members on sales strategies
- Analyses sales data to identify trends and adjust promotional plans
- Conducts performance reviews
- Designs motivational contests and initiatives to encourage high sales performance

Jan 2020 - Feb 2022

Moderator, Content Manager

Tutopt, Kyiv

- Write and Edit Digital Content
- Track Content Performance
- Lead Content Writing Team
- Assist in the Development of Promotional and Marketing Materials



EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS

Sep 2010 - Jul 2014

Bachelor's Degree

Kyiv International University, Kyiv

International Relations

Sep 2014 - Feb 2016

Master's Degree

Kyiv International University, Kyiv

International Relations



REFERENCES

References available on request.



SKILLS

**** Microsoft Word Excel $\star\star\star\star\star$ PowerPoint $\star\star\star\star\star$ Data Management $\star\star\star\star\star$ HTML5, CSS $\star\star\star\star\star$ Cloud computing **** Adaptability **** Business analysis **** Sales **** Budget management $\star\star\star\star\star$ Python